But it is tropical storm force. We'll look at that at the end. Let's put this in motion
cue-009874-02
ridge in the west and it's just going to move over the weekend over us
cue-009876-02
pressing convection and moving the moisture a little further west and then by Monday it
cue-009878
again into Colorado all week long so you can see the south winds here then west
cue-009880
winds around the high and then get to the end of next week it jogs back to the four
cue-009882
winds so moisture has to travel further to get to us and beyond the end of the third or fourth of august
cue-009884
front actually coming down. So we'll see that in just a second.
cue-009886
So we do have that front keeping it cool east of the Rockies on Thursday. That pushes away.
cue-009891
here recovers quickly the next day but here we are up to Thursday and it is still every afternoon
cue-009892
Some drifting off into the plains,
cue-009895
Let's look at precipitable water. It is just very rich. We have a lot of moisture
cue-009899
And then into next week, the moisture is there.
cue-009906
Initially, I can kick off some good thunderstorms.